compareschoolrankings.org 2016-05-04

# School Report Cards by the Fraser Institute - Privacy policy

Home

Privacy policy

**1\. User Agreement**  
By using this website, you signify your consent to and agreement to be bound by these terms, practices and policy. 

**2\. Scope**  
This policy applies to the [compareschoolrankings.org ](http://compareschoolrankings.org/) websites only. 

**3\. Accountability**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the privacy practice on this website please address them in writing to the Director of Communications by Email at [communications@ fraserinstitute.org ](mailto:communications@fraserinstitute.org) or by mail to The Fraser Institute, 4th Floor, 1770 Burrard Street, Vancouver, BC, V6J 3G7. 

**4\. Consent**  
The FRASER INSTITUTE only collects personal information from users if that user voluntarily provides us with such information by or by submitting a question or comment to [compareschoolrankings.org ](http://compareschoolrankings.org/) or to the FRASER INSTITUTE. Users are under no obligation to provide us with this information and may access our websites without providing any personal information. By volunteering this information users agree to its collection for the purposes stated below. 

**5\. Purpose**  
THE FRASER INSTITUTE uses the personal information collected for the following purposes: 

  * To provide users with Email updates (if requested) of events, new research, and activities of the Fraser Institute. 
  * To keep aggregate information on website use. 
  * To obtain user feedback on the website. 

**6\. Collection of Information**  
When submitting a comment by email to the FRASER INSTITUTE'S general mailbox [info@fraserinstitute.org ](mailto:info@fraserinstitute.org) or [communications@fraserinstitute.org ](mailto:communications@fraserinstitute.org) the following personal information is collected: 

  * Email address 

THE FRASER INSTITUTE also collects non-personally identifiable information that becomes available as a result of a user's visit to [compareschoolrankings.org ](http://compareschoolrankings.org/) or the FRASER INSTITUTE'S website. This information includes the following: 

  * The user's IP address (A number automatically assigned to your computer when you visit the website. Our server logs the user's IP address.) 
  * The user's Internet Service Provider (ISP) 
  * The user's Web browser. 
  * Non-personal information about a user's visiting habits MAY also be automatically collected through the use of "cookies." Cookies are computer files that are placed in a user's hard drive to remember any preferences the user may have when surfing the web. They can also tell us how often particular pages are visited. 

**7\. Limiting Use, Disclosure & Retention **  
An individual's personal information is only used in connection with the purposes identified in paragraph 4 of this policy. Individual information collected by THE FRASER INSTITUTE will not be sold or made available to third parties. 

**8\. Safeguards**  
To ensure the protection of personal information collected by us, THE FRASER INSTITUTE employs the following physical, organizational and technological security safeguards: 

  * Access is restricted to the FRASER INSTITUTE offices to employees and authorized individuals of the FRASER INSTITUTE only. 
  * Access to the FRASER INSTITUTE server containing personal information is limited to designated employees of the FRASER INSTITUTE, our web site development company, and ISP and is accessed by use of a password. 
  * The FRASER INSTITUTE server contains firewall protection. Further, all the FRASER INSTITUTE employees are made aware of the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of our users' personal information. 

**9\. Openness**  
The FRASER INSTITUTE is committed to making readily available to individuals information on our policies and practices. 

**10\. Individual Access**  
To review your personal information collected by the FRASER INSTITUTE, please direct your request in writing to the Director of Communications by Email at [communications@ fraserinstitute.org ](mailto:communications@fraserinstitute.org) or by mail to The Fraser Institute, 4th Floor, 1770 Burrard Street, Vancouver, BC, V6J 3G7. 

**11\. Challenging THE FRASER INSTITUTE'S Compliance**  
If you wish to challenge THE FRASER INSTITUTE'S compliance with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act please address your concerns in writing to the Director of Communications by Email at [communications@ fraserinstitute.org ](mailto:communications@fraserinstitute.org) or by mail to The Fraser Institute, 4th Floor, 1770 Burrard Street, Vancouver, BC, V6J 3G7. If you are not satisfied with our response to your challenge, you may submit a complaint to the Federal Privacy Commissioner within six months. Appeals from decisions of the Federal Privacy Commissioner may be made to the Federal Court of Canada within 45 days after the Commissioner's report is sent.
